rndinfo.com 2016-03-11

# Privacy Policy

Radixweb considers privacy of its visitors and participants critical and has thus adopted the below mentioned privacy policy. The policy discloses the practices related to collection of information, both personal and non-personal, its use and its dissemination. Please take a moment to understand these. 

###  Data Collection and Dissemination 

We collect non-personal as well as personal information of our visitors during their visit to the website. The non-personal information collected, like the demographic profile of the visitors, is used to improve the website and enhance the user experience. We also collect IP addresses to diagnose problems with our server, analyze the trends, track the movement of visitors and undertake research and development. Your IP address is used to identify you for the duration of a session and is not linked to any personal information. We also collect additional information like click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, URL of requested resource, query-string portion of URL, request date, request time, other access log fields, user agent information, and navigation data for broad aggregate use. 

When you choose to participate in our site as an interested party you may be requested to furnish some personally identifiable information like your name, your organization’s name, job title, email address, and information about your business. You may also be asked to give your phone and fax numbers. This information is used to notify the interested parties about any opportunities, properties, services, deliver newsletters or to communication with them. Radixweb shall not share the personal information of its interested parties with unaffiliated third parties without obtaining written consent. 

Any and every kind of project specifications or project details collected by Radixweb over the course of providing service shall be viewed as our customer’s intellectual property and treated as highly confidential. We shall not share these details with any third party. To stop receiving any kind of marketing material from Radixweb you can make use of the unsubscribe option given with each mail. 

###  Consent to Processing 

By furnishing your personal information to the website, you imply that you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in India and/or any other country. 

###  Children’s Privacy 

We do not knowingly collect or save any information from children under the age of 15. Public Forums 

Our site may include interactive forums like message boards or chat rooms. It should be noted that any information disclosed in such forums is deemed to be public information. Proper caution should be exercised before disclosing your personal information in such areas. 

###  Legal Disclaimer 

Your personal information may be disclosed when required by law or with bona fide intentions when such action is necessary to conform to the legal requirements or comply with legal process served on the website. We may further use your personal information for our internal marketing and communication purposes. However, we shall not share or disclose this information to unaffiliated or affiliated third parties for whatsoever reasons. To stop receiving any kind of marketing material from Radixweb, you can make use of the unsubscribe option given with each mail. Other than this, your personal information shall be kept highly confidential and shall not be **shared with any third parties.**

Your project and business critical information shall be treated as your intellectual property and kept highly confidential. We shall abstain from sharing this information with any third parties. 

###  Security 

Securing all personal and non-personal information associated with our visitors and participants is a high priority for us. We use secure forms of communication for such data. However, due to the open communication nature of the internet, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Thus, we cannot guarantee that any communication between you and the website will be free from any kind of unauthorized access by third parties and be completely secure. 

###  Sale or Change of Control 

The information collected on the website is an asset of Radixweb and in the event of sale or change of control it will be treated like other assets and transferred accordingly. 

###  Links to Other Websites 

Our site may contain links to other websites or other websites may reference and link to our website. However, Radixweb has no control or does not influence the privacy policy of such other websites and is in no way responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. We, therefore, encourage our visitors and participants to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information. 

###  Acceptance of Policy 

By visiting this website or by receiving services from this website, you are signifying your acceptance of our privacy policy. If you are in disagreement with any of the terms, please do not use our website or our services. We also reserve the rights to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time, at our discretion, by simply posting such change, update, or modification on the website. Your continued use of our site after the changes to the policy terms implies your acceptance of these terms.
